The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Greetings, Senior.
Qiu Siping\NLate Stage Core Formation
So there really is someone skilled in ancient restrictions.
Ancient restrictions ?
Senior, can you help me ?
It's not that difficult
but you must tell me
who placed this restriction on you.
If Senior can break it,
Junior will tell you everything.
I’ll give it a try then.
What is this !?
I won't let you go !
I must use this beast
to lure out the person who knows ancient restrictions.
Fellow cultivator can calm down.
You must be the one
who placed this ancient restriction.
Fellow cultivator, I don't have any any malicious intent.
I have an opportunity to offer you.
We're complete strangers
about to fight each other to death.
Why should I trust you ?
To be honest,
we’re both Late stage Core Formation
hoping to form a Nascent Soul.
If fellow cultivator is willing to lend me a hand,
I can guarantee
that fellow cultivator will be able to form a Nascent Soul.
I know where
you can devour a defenseless Nascent Soul
to greatly increase your chance of forming your Nascent Soul.
I know of a place
where 2 Nascent Souls are in sleeping.
If we succeed,
both of us
will get a Nascent Soul to absorb.
What do you think ?
How do you know about these Nascent Souls ?
One of them
is my Senior Brother.
The other is my master.
Killing your own teacher ?
Nothing unusual,
I’ve done that before.
Master wanted to increase his cultivation
so he planned to refine me.
He thought I was clueless
but I had seen through his scheme long ago.
30 years ago,
while he was in seclusion with my Senior Brother,
I sabotaged them during cultivation
to make them fall asleep.
It's been a few days
since their consciousness were consumed by inner demons.
It's the best time to absorb their Nascent Souls.
What does this have to do with ancient restrictions ?
They cultivated
in an ancient cultivator's cave.
It contains too many restrictions.
If you trigger one, you trigger them all.
If I force my way in,
there might be nothing left for me to obtain.
That’s why I need fellow cultivator’s help.
Master is Early stage Nascent Soul
and Senior Brother had just broken through.
If fellow cultivator can open the restrictions,
then Master’s Nascent Soul
will be yours.
We're almost there.
It's right here.
Entering this gate will trigger a restriction.
I leave everything to fellow cultivator.
This beast is condensed from spiritual energy.
As long as the stone wall keeps supplying energy,
it cannot be killed !
While fighting it,
hidden restrictions in the walls will also launch attacks
that are hard to defend against !
Fellow cultivator, let's first destroy those walls !
Fighting this beast is useless !
As expected,
it wasn't the walls powering the beast
but the beast supplying the entire restriction.
Hiding the restriction's core here
really is the work of a restriction master.
However,
compared to the Ancient God's restrictions,
it's too weak.
Fellow cultivator’s knowledge in restrictions
is really something else !
An Ancient Teleportation Formation ?
Fellow cultivator,
Master and Senior Brother are inside this chamber.
Fellow cultivator, farewell !
Now,
after I craft the Restriction Flag
I will form my Nascent Soul.
I need to place 999 restrictions on this flag
to refine a Restriction Flag of the lowest level.
2 days later
I did it !
What’s going on !?
Could it be ?
Look !
Divine Retribution ? How is this possible ?
Since the ancient cultivation world was destroyed,
Divine Retribution ceased to appear.
Could it be an ancient artifact ?
That would be excellent nourishment
Such massive tribulation clouds...
It must be the appearance of a supreme artifact !
Ancient Gods often triggered Divine Retribution.
The stronger the tribulation,
the more powerful the artifact.
This tribulation is here to destroy the Restriction Flag !
Now or never !
My Golden Core can barely withstand this lightning.
If this continues, it will shatter.
I need to cultivate right now.
Hand over the ancient artifact
and I'll spare your life !
Hand over the artifact !
Be reasonable !
You can’t escape !
Hand over the artifact !
Nothing I ever wanted has ever escaped my grasp !
Nascent Soul ?
Little brat, die !
Break !
Search for him !
A mere Late stage Core Formation
couldn't have vanished into thin air !
Find him !
Dig into the ground if you must !
Since you all tried to kill me,
then you can't blame me for it !
Divine Sense, disperse !
He instantly killed 100 people !?
Retreat !
Wang Lin\NPeak Late stage Core Formation
What kind of luck does this guy have !?
Not only did he survive the Divine Retribution
but he also reached Peak Late stage Core Formation !
Damn it !
Who can I even complain to ?
Congratulations Master,
you turned that misfortune into fortune !
If you devour this Nascent Soul
you will reach Nascent Soul for sure !
The Ji Realm will overpower your peers of the same level.
But it also limits the user.
There has never been
a Ji Realm user who has broken through
above the level of Nascent Soul.
You won't be able to reach higher levels.
My cultivation will stop at Nascent Soul...
But I refuse to accept it !
All the stars were aligned
but the Ji Realm still prevented me from breaking through !
My success comes from the Ji Realm
and now my downfall comes from the Ji Realm !
Master... Fate is unpredictable...
You..
I never believed in fate !
A Divine Retribution is the manifestation of the heavens' rejection towards something. The heavens send a tribulation to eradicate what they don't allow to exist. They appear as tribulation clouds that strike lightining to destroy whatever it is that defied the heavens.\N\NIf the person or object passes the tribulation, it is allowed to exist. Depending on the level of defiance towards the heavens, they can send either a single lightining or multiple clouds with ascending difficulty.\N\NA heaven defying artifact like the Restriction Flag can cause a tribulation to fall but since it was only the first level of 999 restriction is was weak enough be passed with a little help from Wang Lin.\N\NAs the tribulation lighting invaded his body, Wang Lin had no choice but to kill the hundreds of cultivators to swallow their Golden Cores in order to stabilize his cultivation and refine that lightning. That is only possible thanks to the Ancient God Tactic that allows him to devour absurd amounts of spiritual energy without his body exploding.\N\NWhat isn't said here is that he now has a refined tribulation lightning inside his body that he can use to call the tribulation back.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.